celebtv.com 2014-07-02

# Privacy Policy « Celebrity | Style | Family | Music | Home | Fit | Studio | Sports | Gadgets | Teen | Latino

## Privacy Policy

**Last Revised November 16, 2012**

This website and the various content, features and services offered on this website (collectively, the “Site”) are owned and operated by Intersport, Inc. (“Intersport”). Intersport is committed to respecting your online privacy and recognizes your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information (“Personal Information”) you share with us. Intersport has established this Privacy Policy to let you know what information we may collect from you on the Site and how we may use and share that information. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the Site, you agree to accept the terms of our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please do not use the Site. Except as provided in the “Your California Privacy Rights” section below, this Privacy Policy applies only to information that we collect on the Site and does not apply to information which we may collect by other means.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

The following only applies to California residents who have an established business relationship with Intersport.

If we collect your name or other Personal Information from you (whether online or offline), and you have given us permission to share your Personal Information by clicking on the appropriate box or button on the Site, we may occasionally make that Personal Information available to other affiliated companies, or to other third parties who have products or services that we believe will be of interest to you, for their direct marketing purposes. If you later decide that you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these companies for their direct marketing purposes, please e-mail [privacy@celebtv.com](mailto:privacy@celebtv.com). Your opt out request will be processed within thirty (30) days of the date on which we receive it. For more information on how your Personal Information is collected, used and shared, please read the remainder of this Privacy Policy.

**Personal Information**

**Information We May Collect**

Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a [home](http://www.celebtv.com/c/topics/home "home") or other physical address, a phone number, and/or an email address . In general, you can visit the Site without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself. However, in order to access certain information, services or features that may be contained on the Site, we may require you to provide Personal Information as described above. For example, we will collect certain Personal Information if you choose to subscribe to a mailing list, register for an account, participate in special offers, sweepstakes or other promotions, sign up for our chat rooms, message boards or blogs, or send questions or comments to us via e-mail.

We may also collect certain demographic information (such as gender, age income, education, profession) and information about your interests and preferences (“preferences information”). In many cases, such demographic and preferences information is optional. In other cases, such as online surveys, we collect this information on an anonymous basis. However, if we link any demographic or preferences information to any Personal Information, then such demographic and preferences information will be treated as Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

For some features of the Site, you may be able to submit information about other people. For example, if you wish to e-mail a video from the Site to a friend, you will submit your friend’s e-mail address, your e-mail address, and an optional message to that person which may also have personal information within it. We will use and store any such information that we collect from you about another person only to the extent necessary to carry out your request, and we will not use such information for any other purpose.

**How We May Use Your Information**

If you provide us with Personal Information, we may retain and use that information for several purposes. For example, if you sign up for the CelebTV.com celebrity news updates, we will use your Personal Information to notify you when news breaks. We also may use the information to communicate with you about new features, products or services and/or improved services that we offer. In addition, we may use your Personal Information in order to process and fulfill any transactions or services that you request, including any customary follow-up or confirmation communications regarding such transactions, entering you into a sweepstakes, establishing an account for you, responding to your questions or comments, or sending e-mails to our mailing list subscribers. We may also use Personal Information to ensure compliance with our policies and applicable law. In addition, we may send you periodic communications by e-mail or regular mail, such as news updates, special offers or information on our products or services, if you have chosen to receive such communications. If you later wish to opt out of receiving such promotional e-mails from us at any time, simply follow the instructions for doing so in the e-mails that you receive from us. We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Site, such as service announcements or similar administrative or transactional messages, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

**With Whom We May Share Your Information**

We may sometimes use other businesses to perform certain services for us and functions on our Site, such as maintaining the Site and our mailing lists, processing orders and delivering products, sending postal mail, providing marketing assistance and data analysis, sending promotional e-mails, collecting the aggregate information described below, and tracking the use of our website through the use of cookies as described below. We may allow access to or provide Personal Information to those businesses when that information is necessary for them to complete a requested transaction or otherwise perform their duties. Intersport will take reasonable steps to ensure that these third-party service providers are obligated to protect Personal Information on Intersport’s behalf. Intersport, however, does not bear any responsibility for any actions or policies of third parties.

In addition, if you have given us permission to share your Personal Information by clicking on the appropriate box or button on the Site, we may make your Personal Information available to our parent or other affiliated companies, or to other third parties who have products or services that we believe will be of interest to you, for their direct marketing purposes. If you later decide that you do not want us to share your Personal Information with these companies for their direct marketing purposes, please e-mail [privacy@celebtv.com](mailto:privacy@celebtv.com). As Intersport develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that Intersport or all of its assets are acquired, customer information would be one of the transferred assets.

We reserve the right to disclose visitor information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, [contact](http://www.celebtv.com/contact "contact"), or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) our rights or property, other visitors, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. We also reserve the right to disclose visitor information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

**Aggregate Information**

From time to time, we, our marketing partners, and other businesses associated with us may collect general, non-personal, statistical information about the use of the Site, such as how many visitors visit a specific page on the Site, how long they stay on that page, the types of searches run on the site, and which hyperlinks, if any, they “click” on. We collect this information through the use of “cookies” and other tracking technologies, which are discussed in greater detail below. We collect this information in order to determine which areas of the Site are most popular, enhance the Site for visitors, and to determine consumer preferences for marketing purposes. We may group this information into aggregate visitor data in order to describe the use of the Site to our existing or potential business partners, sponsors, advertisers or other third parties, or in response to a government request. We may also group demographic and preferences information and responses to surveys that we collect from visitors into aggregate data for the same purposes. However, please be assured that this aggregate data will in no way personally identify you or any other visitors to the Site.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to you by DoubleClick, our Web advertising partner. Information about your visit to this site, such as number of times you have viewed an ad (but not your name, address, or other personal information), is used to serve ads to you on this site. For more information about DoubleClick, cookies, and how to “opt-out”, please click here. (http://www.doubleclick.net/us/corporate/privacy)

**Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies**

Some of our web pages utilize “cookies” and other tracking technologies. A cookie is a small text file that a website transfers to an individual’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. For example, we may use cookies to collect information about website activity and to enhance your experience on our site. We do not collect credit card information and never save credit card information in cookies. Most browsers allow you to control cookies, including whether or not to accept them and how to remove them. You may set most browsers to notify you if you receive a cookie, or you may choose to block cookies with your browser. However, please be aware that some features of the Site may not function properly or may be slower if you refuse cookies. Our cookies may contain Personal Information and such cookies may be shared with our affiliates and other companies if you authorize such action. You may occasionally get cookies from our advertisers or other third parties with links on the Site. We do not control these cookies. The use of advertising cookies sent by third-party servers is standard in the Internet industry. These cookies will only collect aggregate information as described above and will not collect or transfer Personal Information unless authorized by you.

Tracking technologies may record information such as Internet domain and host names; Internet protocol (IP) addresses; browser software and operating system types; clickstream patterns; and dates and times that our Site is accessed. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the web. Web servers, the big computers that “serve up” webpages, automatically identify your computer by its IP address. It is not our practice to link the information we record using tracking technologies to any Personal Information you submit while on the Site. However, we reserve the right to use IP addresses and other tracking technologies to identify a visitor only when we feel it is necessary to enforce compliance with the Site’s policies, to protect the Service, our customers or others, or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser.

**Links to Other Sites; Public Venues**

Please be aware that when you are on the Site, you could be directed to other sites that are beyond our control. These other sites may send their own cookies to visitors, collect data or solicit Personal Information. The privacy policies of these other sites may be significantly different from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites and cannot guarantee the security of any of your Personal Information collected there.

Please keep in mind that whenever you give out Personal Information on a “public” venue online (for example, in a blog, message board or chat room), that information can be collected and used by people you do not know. If you choose to voluntarily disclose information in any blog, message board, chat room or similar forum that may be available on the Site, the protections of this Privacy Policy will not cover such disclosure of information. We urge you to use caution when disclosing any Personal Information on these venues. We are not responsible and will not be liable for any opinions, content or other materials posted by users on any such venues, or for the use by other visitors or third parties of any information or content you may post to such venues.

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. However, there is some risk in transmitting information electronically. The personal information collected on the Site is stored within databases that we control. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards, such as firewalls and encryption technology, to protect your information. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can be guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. By supplying us with information, you acknowledge these risks and signify that you have voluntarily chosen to provide the information despite the inherent risks involved.

**Updating Your Information**

Any requests that we correct, [update](http://www.celebtv.com/c/update "update"), or remove your information in our databases, should be directed via email to [privacy@celebtv.com](mailto:privacy@celebtv.com), or via regular mail to:

CelebTV  
20 W. Kinzie, Suite 1600  
Chicago, IL 60657  
Attn: Privacy Policy Department.

After receiving a request to change your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your Personal Information stored in databases we actively use to operate our website will be updated, corrected, changed, or deleted, as appropriate, as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information we remove from or change in our active website databases. We may retain such information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, and enforce our terms and conditions of use. In addition, it may not be technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us. A copy of your personal information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate.

**Children’s Privacy**

This Site is not intended for use by children under 13. We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from anyone under 13 years of age, except for the limited circumstances described below. In the event a child under the age of 13 submits a question to us on the Site and identifies his or her age, we may use the child’s e-mail address for the sole purpose of responding to the child’s question on a one-time-only basis. However, we will not use the child’s e-mail address to recontact the child and we will delete it from our records once we have responded. If we become aware that we have unknowingly collected Personal Information from a child under the age of 13, we will make commercially reasonable efforts to delete such information from our database.

**Changes to Our Privacy Policy**

The terms of this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes to this Privacy Policy by posting a notice on the homepage of the Site for a reasonable period of time after such changes are made that this Privacy Policy has been updated, and by changing the “Last Modified” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to check this page periodically for any changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes.

**Governing Law**

Intersport makes no representation that this Privacy Policy and such practices comply with the laws of any other country than the United States. Visitors who use the Site and reside outside the United States do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws, if and to the extent local laws are applicable. If you reside outside of the United States, by using our Site, you consent to the transfer and use of your information outside your country.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Privacy Policy, please e-mail us at [privacy@celebtv.com](mailto:privacy@celebtv.com), or at our contact information below.

CelebTV  
20 W. Kinzie, Suite 1600  
Chicago, IL 60657  
Attn: Privacy Policy Department
